Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Facilities use records, Circa 1979 - 2006; Series 15
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 16; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 15; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 18; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 20; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 22; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 24; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 1; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 3; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 6; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 Ocotber 7; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 8; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 14; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 23; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 26; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 21; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 25; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 28; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 29; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 September 30; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Archibald Motley Opening Reception, 1992 October 2; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 10; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 11; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 14; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 13; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 15; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 16; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 18; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 19; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Facilities Records, Circa 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Facilities Records, Circa 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Dudley Memorial Lecture and Reception, 1992 Fall; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 21; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 1992 October 22; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 25; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Facilities Records, Circa 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 27; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 28; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 October 31; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - Friend Gala, 1992 October 30; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Fall Preview Opening Reception, 1992 September 11; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 1; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 2; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 5; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - Bill Bodine Farwell Dinnerr, Circa 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 7; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 8; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 65)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 10; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 66)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 12; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 67)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 13; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 68)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 14; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 69)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 15; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 70)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 16; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 71)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 17; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 72)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 19; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 73)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 18; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 74)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 21; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 75)
  - Facilities Records, 1992 November 23; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 76)
  - Holiday Open House, 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 77)
  - Holiday Open House Finances, 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 78)
  - Reverberations-Invites, Circa 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 79)
  - AT+T December 8 Invites, Circa 1992; Series 15 (Box 53, Folder 80)
  - Facility Use, 1995; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Facility Use, 1996; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Facility Use, 199; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Attendance Reports (1 of 3), 1997; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Attendance Reports (2 of 3), 1997; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Attendance Reports (3 of 3), 1997; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Invoices (1 of 2), 1998-1999; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Invoices (2 of 2), 1998-1999; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Facility Service Fees (1 of 3), 1999; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Facility Service Fees (2 of 3), 1999; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Facility Service Fees (3 of 3), 1999; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Budget (1 of 2), 2000; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Budget (2 of 2), 2000; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Operational Plan, 2006; Series 15 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Banquet/Function Reservations, 1994; Series 15 (Box 118, Item 1)
  - Banquet/Function Reservations, 1995; Series 15 (Box 119, Item 1)
  - Banquet/Function Reservations, 1996; Series 15 (Box 120, Item 1)
  - Banquet/Function Reservations, 1997; Series 15 (Box 121, Item 1)
  - Banquet/Function Reservations, 1998; Series 15 (Box 122, Item 1)
  - Banquet/Function Reservations, 1999; Series 15 (Box 123, Item 1)